{
    "subject": "resource/The_Lashes",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The Lashes are from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6417245268821716,
            "question": "Where are The Lashes from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.555059552192688,
            "question": "What country is The Lashes from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3849465847015381,
            "question": "Are The Lashes popular in other countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33307942748069763,
            "question": "What is The Lashes known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2513381242752075,
            "question": "What is the history of The Lashes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21270599961280823,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about The Lashes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19318079948425293,
            "question": "Is The Lashes a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17182417213916779,
            "question": "Are there any famous musicians in The Lashes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13894475996494293,
            "question": "Has The Lashes released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10170239210128784,
            "question": "What genre of music does The Lashes play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Lashes are from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9073_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has The Lashes released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9073_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous musicians in The Lashes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9073_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is The Lashes a band?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9073_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9073_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that the United States is a pioneer in the global lash extension industry and a key player in the eyelash extension supply chain with a large population of bulk lash production in North America.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention several eyelash suppliers based in the United States, such as Levi Lashes. This supports the statement that \"The Lashes are from the United States.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}